Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Paper Production Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Frontline: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 13)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 14)
    - Primeras Planas ¯ La Jornada, 9/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 15)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 9/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 16)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 17)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 18)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 19)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 20)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 21)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 22)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 10/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 23)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 24)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 25)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 26)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 27)
    - Primeras Planas ¯ La Jornada, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 28)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 29)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 9/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 30)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 31)
    - Las Planas ¯ La Jornada, 5/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 32)
    - Las Planas ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 33)
    - Caricaturas ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 34)
    - Chiapas ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 35)
    - Colosio ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 36)
    - Corrupcion ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 37)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 38)
    - Salinas ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 39)
    - Varios ¯ El Financiero, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 40)
    - Primeras Planas ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 41)
    - Caricaturas ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 42)
    - Chiapas ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 43)
    - Colosio ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 44)
    - Corrupcion ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 45)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 46)
    - Salinas ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 47)
    - Varios ¯ El Financiero, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 48)
    - Primeras Planas ¯ El Financiero, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 49)
    - Caricaturas ¯ El Financiero, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 50)
    - Chiapas ¯ El Financiero, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 51)
    - Colosio ¯ El Financiero, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 70, Folder 52)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 1)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 2)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 3)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 4)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 5)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 6)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 7)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 8)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 9)
    - Primeras Planas ¯ Reforma, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 10)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 11)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 12)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 13)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 14)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 15)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 16)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 17)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 18)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 19)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 20)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 21)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 22)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 23)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 24)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 25)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 26)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 27)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 28)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 29)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 30)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 31)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 32)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 33)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 71, Folder 34)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 1)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 2)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 3)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 4)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 5)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 6)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 7)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 8)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 9)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 10)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 11)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 12)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 13)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 14)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 15)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 16)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 17)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 18)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 19)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 20)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 21)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 22)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 23)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 24)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 25)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 26)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 27)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 28)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 72, Folder 29)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 1)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 2)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 3)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 4)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 5)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 6)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 7)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 2/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 8)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 9)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 10)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 11)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 12)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 13)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 14)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 15)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 3/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 16)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 17)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 18)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 19)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 20)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 21)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 22)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 23)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 24)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 25)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 26)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 27)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 28)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 29)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 30)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 31)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 32)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 33)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 34)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 35)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 36)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 37)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 38)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 39)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 40)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 41)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 42)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 43)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 44)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 45)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 46)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 47)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 48)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 49)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 50)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 51)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 52)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 53)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 54)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 55)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 56)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 57)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 58)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 59)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 60)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 61)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 62)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 63)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 73, Folder 64)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 1)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 2)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 3)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 4)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 5)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 6)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 7)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 8)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 9)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 10)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 11)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 12)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 13)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 14)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 15)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 16)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 17)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 18)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 19)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 20)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 21)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 22)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 23)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 24)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 25)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 26)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 27)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 28)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 29)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 30)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 31)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 74, Folder 32)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 1)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 2)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 4/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 3)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 4)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 5)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 6)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 7)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 8)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 9)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 10)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 5/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 11)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 12)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 13)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 14)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 15)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 16)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 17)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 18)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 6/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 19)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 20)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 21)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 22)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 23)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 24)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 25)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 26)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 27)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 28)
    - Salinas ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 29)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 30)
    - Colosio ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 31)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 32)
    - Chiapas ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 33)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 34)
    - Varios ¯ Reforma, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 35)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 36)
    - Salinas ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 37)
    - Corrupcion ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 38)
    - Colosio ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 39)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 40)
    - Chiapas ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 41)
    - Caricaturas ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 42)
    - Varios ¯ Financiero, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 75, Folder 43)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 1)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 2)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 3)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 4)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 5)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 6)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 7)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 8/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 8)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 9)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 10)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 11)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 12)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 13)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 14)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 15)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 9/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 16)
    - 1ra Plana ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 17)
    - Salinas ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 18)
    - Corrupcion ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 19)
    - Colosio ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 20)
    - Narcotrafico ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 21)
    - Chiapas ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 22)
    - Caricaturas ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 23)
    - Varios ¯ La Jornada, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 24)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4036, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 25)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4037, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 26)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4038, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 27)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4039, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 28)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4040, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 29)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4041, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 30)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4042, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 31)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4044, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 32)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4045, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 33)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4046, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 34)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4047, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 35)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4048, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 36)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4049, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 37)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4050, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 38)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4051, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 39)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4052, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 40)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4053, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 41)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4054, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 42)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4055, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 43)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4056, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 44)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4057, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 45)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4058, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 46)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4059, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 47)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4060, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 48)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4061, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 49)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4062, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 50)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4063, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 51)
    - La Jornada ¯ #4064, 12/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 76, Folder 52)
    - Magazine Research: Stills to Film (Small Book) From ¯ Extra! Contenido¯ "Salinas y Su Mexico", 1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 1)
    - Magazine Research: Extra! Contenido ¯ "Salinas y Su Mexico" (Complete Book), 1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 2)
    - Magazine Research: Impacto ¯ Edicion Especial: El Presidente de los Tiempos Dificiles, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 3)
    - Magazine Research: La Guillotina #30, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Research: La Jornada Semanal #295, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 5)
    - Magazine Research: Espaz #4, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 6)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2357, 5/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 7)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2355, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 8)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2353, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 9)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2352, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 10)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2351, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 11)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2350, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 12)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2348, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 13)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2335, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 14)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2334, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 15)
    - Magazine Research: Tiempo #2333 (2 copies), 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 16)
    - Magazine Research: Ahuizote #18, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 17)
    - Magazine Research: Actual #28, 1/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 18)
    - Magazine Research: La Crisis #17, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 19)
    - Magazine Research: Forbes, 8/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 20)
    - Magazine Research: San Francisco Examiner Magazine, 7/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 21)
    - Magazine Research: De Para Polanco #3, 6¯8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 22)
    - Magazine Research: Guiri, Vol. 2, #4, 1/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 23)
    - Magazine Research: Mexico Desconocido, #217, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 24)
    - Magazine Research: Boletin #53 Editorial De El Colegio De Mexico: 1¯2, 1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 25)
    - Magazine Research: Ecos De Mexico #11, 10/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 26)
    - Magazine Research: Polemica #9, 7/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 27)
    - Magazine Research: Hojas De Utopia #4, 10/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 28)
    - Magazine Research: Sin Mascaras: Autumn, 1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 29)
    - Magazine Research: Rotativo #2863, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 30)
    - Magazine Research: Ojararsca #37, 10/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 31)
    - Magazine Research: Ojararsca #35, #36, 9/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 32)
    - Magazine Research: Quehacer Politico #744 (2 copies), 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 33)
    - Magazine Research: Quehacer Politico #708, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 34)
    - Magazine Research: Epoca: Edicion Especial #238, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 35)
    - Magazine Research: Epoca #236, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 36)
    - Magazine Research: Impacto #2389, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 37)